[
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "あ",
    "back": "a",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "い",
    "back": "i",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "う",
    "back": "u",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "え",
    "back": "e",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "お",
    "back": "o",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "か",
    "back": "ka",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "き",
    "back": "ki",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "く",
    "back": "ku",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "け",
    "back": "ke",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "こ",
    "back": "ko",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "さ",
    "back": "sa",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "し",
    "back": "shi",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "す",
    "back": "su",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "せ",
    "back": "se",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "そ",
    "back": "so",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "back": "ta",
    "front": "た",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "back": "chi",
    "front": "ち",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "back": "tsu",
    "front": "つ",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "て",
    "back": "te",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "と",
    "back": "to",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "な",
    "back": "na",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "に",
    "back": "ni",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "ぬ",
    "back": "nu",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "ね",
    "back": "ne",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "の",
    "back": "no",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "は",
    "back": "ha",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "ひ",
    "back": "hi",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "ふ",
    "back": "fu",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "へ",
    "back": "he",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "ほ",
    "back": "ho",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "ま",
    "back": "ma",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "み",
    "back": "mi",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "む",
    "back": "mu",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "め",
    "back": "me",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "も",
    "back": "mo",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "や",
    "back": "ya",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "ゆ",
    "back": "yu",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "よ",
    "back": "yo",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "ら",
    "back": "ra",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "り",
    "back": "ri",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "る",
    "back": "ru",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "れ",
    "back": "re",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  },
  {
    "name": "hiragana",
    "front": "ろ",
    "back": "ro",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": null,
    "tag": [0]
  }
]
